我没事 直接回家吧
I'm okay,let's just go home.
我要带你去医院检查下
You're getting checked out.
我就是在雪地里摔了一跤
I tripped on the ice.
其他8个人也摔倒了
Eight other kids tripped.
这太丢脸了
This is embarrassing.
你说就是跟朋友玩
You said you were just gonna hang with your friends.
结果我一转身 你就到雪地上去
I turn around and you're out there on the ice.
我没事
I'm fine.
你自己不知道
You don't know that.
你摔得很惨
You fell. Awkwardly.
不是那样的
No, I didn'T.
你连摔跤都不会
You don't know how to fall.
我16岁了 摔过很多次
I'm 16,I've been falling a lot.
早就学会怎么做了
I think I'm getting the hang of it.
而且我检查过了
And I checked.
让医生检查
And now the doctors are gonna check.
你不觉得太大惊小怪了吗?
You don't think that you're over reacting?
不是每次受伤 都要你来照料
I don't need youto fix every boo-boo.
那就别受伤
Then stop getting them.
我只是跟朋友一起玩 我们很开心
I was just playing aroundwith my friends.I was having fun.
你不能那样
You know you can't do that.
我不能开心吗?
Oh, I can't have fun?
你知道我什么意思
You know what I mean.
我要跟你的朋友谈谈
I'm gonna have a talkwith your friends and
- 不 不行,- 告诉他们不要...
- no!No.,- tell them that they need to stop--
你会把他们吓坏的
I don't want you freaking them out.
好吧 我们去医院
Fine.Fine, we'll goto the hospital,
医生会告诉你 我没事
but they're gonna tell you that I'm fine.
还会叫你别担心...
And they're gonna tell you that you don't need to worry about...
妈妈!
mom!
妈妈?妈妈
Mom? Mom.
有人吗!
Hello!
妈妈 醒醒
Mom, you gotta wake up.
没人在这
No one's coming.
妈妈!
Mom!
911 有什么紧急事故?
911, what is your emergency?
在金斯敦市郊的公路上发生了车祸,(金斯敦: 加拿大安大略南部城市)
We got into an accident along the canal road just outside kingston.
我妈妈昏迷了
My mom's unconscious.
你受伤了吗?
are you okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
妈妈 妈妈
MoM.Mom.
-=怪杰医生豪斯=-,第三季 第14集 "感觉木然","Insensitive"
House.M.D,Season 3 Episode 14
foreman在哪?
Where's foreman?
他在楼下某处吧
He's down here somewhere.
某处 多谢你帮忙
Somewhere.Very helpful.
你知道他今晚几点下班吗?
Do you have any idea when he's getting out tonight?
某时吧
Sometime.
我知道你说不准 但是估计呢?
I realize you can't predict, I just thought you might be able to estimate.
今天情人节
It's valentine's day.
我要给他个惊喜 一起离开
I've planned a surprise getaway.
- 离开,- 唔
- Getaway.,- Mmm-hmm.
走开 走 开
Getaway.Get away.
我妈妈怎样了?
Is my mom okay?
送去手术室了
She's gone to surgery.
Foreman.
Foreman
你女朋友想知道
Your girl friend wants to know
你情人节有没有空 表现得惊讶点
if you're available for valentine'S.Act surprised.
你下来干什么?
What are you doing down here?
发生了暴风雪 急诊室缺人
There's a snowstorm.E.R.'S short staffed.
我们都应该来帮忙的
We're all supposed to be here.
你也应该来的
You're supposed to be here.
你是个混蛋 表现得惊讶点
And you're an ass.Act surprised.
可能会有点刺痛
This could sting a little.
能快点吗
Ow!Can we hurry thi
- 我得确保...,- 慢慢来
make sure that-- take your time.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
Hannah morganthal.
Hannah morganthal
你得了无痛症 hannah morganthal
You have cipa, hannah morganthal.
我没得
No, I don'T.
要照X光看有没有内伤
We have to do x-rays to make sure you don't have internal injuries.
查血象确定没有感染
Blood tests to make sure no infections.
还要看脑电图是否异常
Eeg for neurological anomalies.
还有 脊髓神经切片
And...biopsy a spinal nerve.
先天性的痛觉丧失
Whoa whoa whoa.Congenital insensitivity to pain is
世上最罕见的病症
one of the rarest conditions on the planet.
全球好像只有 60例...
There's only been about...60 documented caseS...
对 我有7个理由相信她是其中之一
yeah, and I have seven reasons to think she's one of them.
她自己说不是
She says she's not.
这就是第一个理由
That's reason number one.
我们没说她就知道那是什么病了
She knew what it was without us telling her.
第二 她全身都被雪弄湿了却没有颤抖
Two, she's still wet from the snow, but she's not shivering.
那很奇怪
That's odd.
除非她不会出汗或者感觉不到冷热
Unless she can't sweat or feel hot and cold.
救护车上很暖和
The ambulance was warm.
我想见我妈妈
I want to see my mother.
第三 嘴唇和舌头上有伤疤
Three, scarring around the lips and tongue.
是小时候没有感觉 自己咬伤的
When she was a baby, she chew on herself without feeling it.
我小时候从窗户摔下去过
I fell through a window when I was a kid.
第四 你在清理伤口的时候
Four, when you cleaned the wound,
她的脚没有避开清洁棉布 而是迎上去
she flexed into the cleaner instead of away from it.
从没有过痛觉的话 很难假装
It's hard to fake pain when you've never felt it.
来个跳跃性思维 Morganthal女士
Takes an imaginative leap, ms.Morganthal.
这是个犹太人名吧
That's one of them jew names.
德系犹太人患病率更高
Ashkenazis are a higher risk group.
可是 她说了她没有这种病
One the other hand, she says she doesn't have it.
如果以前没诊断出来的话,她不可能活到现在
And she'd be dead by now if she'd never been diagnosed.
犹太人杀害了上帝
They killed our lord.
你还相信他们?
You gonna trust them?
她想见她妈妈
She wants to see her mom.
她知道如果承认有无痛症 就哪也去不了
If she admits having cipa, she knows we're not letting her go anywhere
只能去做一堆检测
without a battery of tests.
你说有七个理由的
You said you had seven reasons.
我那是随便说说的
I pulled a number out of the air.
怎么 五个理由不够吗?
What, five isn't enough?
五个差劲的理由不够
Five lame reasons aren'T.
我会尽快带她去见她妈妈
I'm taking her to see her mom as soon as--
如果六个理由还不够 我可以再敲她一下
I can hit her again if six isn't enough.
做检查
Do the tests.
我要从急诊室抽身
Need to bail on the E.R.
有个病人
I got a case.
你喷了香水?
Why are you wearing perfume?
是真的有病人
Is this a real case or one of those imaginary cases
还是你无聊想象出来的?
that happen when you're bored?
- 无痛症,- 无痛症是个诊断
- Cipa.,- Cipa is a diagnosis.
诊断是最后下的结论
Diagnoses happen at the end of cases.
她不知道自己的身体状况
She's got no idea what's going on in her body.
肯定有什么不对劲的
There's gotta be something wrong.
换句话说 她可能很健康
In other words, she could be perfectly healthy,
你只是好奇 怎么有人不会痛
but you're curious about me one
而你自己一天到晚痛
who can't feel pain because you always feel pain.
所以你想探究
So you wanna go exploring.
她出了车祸
She was in a car accident.
她要做x光 血象 脑电图 神经切片
She needs x-rays, blood tests, eeg, nerve biopsy.
我还注意到 尽管今早大雪纷飞
I also note that, although snow was coming down in sheets this morning,
你却没戴帽子 只戴了耳罩
you left your hat at home and used ear muffs.
你检测是不是为了...
Do your tests except for the--
当大家都在担心能否来上班时
so while everyone else was just worrying about getting in,
你却只关心帽子压坏发型
you were concerned with hat-head.
相亲从不是好主意
Blind dates are never a good idea.
你披披肩的唯一理由,就是能从人群中一眼认出你
Only reason to wear a scarf like that is as a beacon to identify you in a crowd.
做你的测试吧
Do your tests.
除了神经切片
Except the nerve biopsy.
- 我需要切片的结果,- 那样她有可能瘫痪
- I need the nerve biopsy.,- You'd risk paralyzing her.
但这是神经疾病
But it's neurological.
你没有证据
You have no evidence of that.
她摔倒了
She tripped.
你还有其他任何证据吗?
Do you have any evidence other than the fact that
除了笨拙的无痛症病人在雪天摔倒
a typically clumsy cipa patient tripped on an icy day?
如果脑电图有问题 我们再讨论
If the eeg reveals a problem, we can talk then.
你可以把披肩扔家里
You could have left the scarf at home and
只要告诉他你一脸绝望就很好认
just told him you'd be wearing a look of desperation.
左中央区和右枕区有尖频
Spiking on leads c3 and o2.
- 她可能会发作,- 喂
- She could be going into a seizure.,- Hello.
应该有更简单的解释
I think there's a simpler explanation.
你们什么都查不出来的
You're not gonna find anything.
我没事 我要见我妈妈!
I'm fine!I wanna see my mom!
给她打镇定剂
So sedate her.
她不会答应的
She won't consent.
她才十几岁
She's a teenager.
没有爸爸 妈妈还在手术
No dad,mom's still in surgery.
你想让我们怎么做 按倒她?
What do you want us to do,hold her down?
给她注射镇定剂之后
Only until you inject her with a sedative.
你才能放开她
Then you can let her go.
-我们试过了,-真的?
- We tried.,- Seriously?
她力气很大 不停挣扎
She's strong and doesn't care.
我怕还没等注入镇静剂
We'd have broken something before
就会先伤害到她的身体
we could get her to sit still enough to inject her.
那就打断她的手
So break her arm.
她不会在意的
She won't mind.
你真变态
You're cranky.
我很痛
I'm in pain.
走 去打折她的手
Come on,let's go break her arm.
那个小护士 你女朋友
Nurse shortie,your biz-nitch.
你还准备跟她耗多久?
How long you gonna waste her time?
真庆幸我们走的路有尽头
So glad we're walking somewhere.
再走60英尺 就可以结束这段对话
Another 60 feet and this conversation is over.
等这段研究结束 Cameron会找到个伴
When you guys are out of this program, cameron will find somebody,
Chase会找到8个 而你就孤单一人了
chase will find eight somebodies, and you'll be alone.
还有30英尺
30 feet.
你不断地约会
You'll date and you'll date.
但你是终极达尔文主义者
But you're the ultimate darwinian.
努力奋斗
You've got to fight for everything.
身边有人只会拖累你
Anybody else would just slow you down.
是
Yeah.
但我还和她在一起 不是吗?
I'm still with her,aren't I?
是
Yeah.
我猜那是因为她没给你分手的借口
I can only imagine it's because she hasn't given you
而你也没有勇气认清现实
an excuse to break up and you don't have the guts to recognize your own reality.
我要见我妈妈!
I wanna see my mother!
又见面了
Hi again.
我要是好声好气跟你说话
Not sure I can say this without being condescending,
你会误以为我尊敬你...
but then you'd get the false impression that I respect you,so...
你是个孩子
you're a kid.
你很害怕 拖延时间
You're scared,you're stalling.
成熟点
Grow up.
我没有害怕
I'm not scared.
我从不害怕
I'm never scared.
看吧 这话多幼稚啊?
See?How juvenile was that?
你没有痛觉
You can't feel pain.
只能感到快乐
Nothing left but pleasure.
告诉我这种感觉多棒?
Why don't you tellehow wonderful that is?
糟透了
It sucks.
比持续疼痛好得多吧
Better than being in pain all the time.
到椅子上去
Get in the chair.
我每天早上都检查眼睛
Every morningI have to check my eyes to make sure
看睡觉的时候有没有把角膜抓伤
I didn't scratch a cornea in my sleep.
哦 天哪 别说了
Oh, god, stop.
泪流成河了
I'm in a pool of tears here.
- 我不能哭,- 我也不行
- I can't cry,- neither can I.
每天早上 都要看下眼睛有没有黄疸
Every morning, I check my eyesfor jaundice.
以免维柯丁最后弄坏了肝
In case the vicodin's finally shot my liver.
不检查下脚趾有没肿 就哪也不能跑去
I can't run anywhere without examining all my toes for swelling.
我不能跑
I can't run.
男生不能搂我太久  因为我身体会过热
Boys can't hold me for too long because I can overheat.
女生不能搂我太久 因为只付一小时工钱
Girls can't hold me for too long because I only pay for an hour.
需要闹铃提醒自己上厕所
I need an alarm on my watch to remind meto go to the bathroom.
在想到这主意之前,你知道有多少回羞辱的事情么?
You know how many humiliating experiences before I thought of that?
厕所离办公室50英尺
The bathroom's 50 feet from my office.
喝个水都要权衡利弊
Every drink of water,I weigh the pros and cons.
什么事做完后 都要自我检查一番
After everything I do,I self-check.
嘴巴 舌头 牙床上有没有割伤
Mouth, tongue, gums, for cuts.
牙少了没 体温是否正常
Count teeth,check temperature.
手指 脚趾 关节是不是有肿起
Fingers, toes, and jointsfor swelling.
有没有擦伤到皮
Skin for bruises.
我挨过枪子
I got shot.
三岁时坐在炉子上
I sat on the stove when I was three.
要欣赏一下印的圈圈么?
Wanna see the coil marks?
- 好,- 你觉得我在扯谎?
- Yeah.,- You think I'm lying?
你觉得我想观赏你屁屁 犹太人用词?
You think I just wanna check out your tuchus, as your people would say?
把她放好 做见鬼的测试
Get in the chair and run the damn tests.
如果她再动弹 给她用氧化亚氮,(氧化亚氮: 俗名笑气 麻醉剂)
If she moves again,give her nitrous.
你中弹 不是因为腿痛 是因为你混蛋
You weren't shot because of leg pain, you were shot because you're a jerk.
这两者不无联系
Some think the two are connected.
他没必要这么做
He didn't have to do that.
是 他这么做了
Yeah, he did.
我确实病了?
I'm sick?
没有 脑电图没有问题
No, you eeg was normal.
X光片上没有骨折
X-ray showed no breaks.
血液检查没有显示感染
Blood testshowed no infections.
尿检没有...
Urine indicated no...
hannah?
Hannah?
来人
Call a code!
哦 天哪
Oh, god.
需要冰袋和降温毯
Need ice packs and cooling blankets.
有盐水么?
Got saline in there?
她没有发红或流汗
She's not flush,she's not sweating.
- 你肯定是-,- 她体温105 (40.5摄氏度)
- You must be-,- she has a temperatureof 105.
哇 她的确是病了
Wow, she's actually sick.
把她的体温降下来了
We got her temperature down below boiling.
可能是感染
Could be infection.
不 腰椎穿刺检测到正常的蛋白质,没有白细胞
No, lp showed normal proteinsand no white blood cells.
高胆红素
High bilirubin.
可能问题在肝脏
Could be a liver problem.
不是 转氨酶正常
Nope, transaminases were normal.
磕药
Could be drugs.
她11岁就吸大麻
She's smoked pot since she was 11.
也不是
No again.
毒物筛检没有问题
Tox screen was clean.
我们反着做
We're doing this case backwards.
做了检查然后她得病了
We do the tests and then she gets sick?
也许是我们对她做了什么
Maybe we did something to her.
她在检查后得病
Maybe she got sick after the tests.
应该重新做检测
We should re-run them.
脊髓神经切片
And biopsy a spinal nerve.
因为发烧 你要让她冒瘫痪的危险?
You wanna risk paralysis because she's got a fever?
冒瘫痪的危险,因为不知道什么引起了发烧
I want to risk paralysis because I don't know what's causing the fever.
- 是神经问题,- 是发烧!
- It's a neurological,- It's a fever!
在无痛症患的身上
In a cipa patient.
明显她身上情况有变化 在发出信号
Obviously, things are a little different in her upstairs wiring.
从出生起一直如此
And have been since the day she was born.
是 病症巧妙地躲藏着
Yeah.It's much more likely that whatever it is was cleverly
直到你们做完测试
waited in hiding until you guys were done testing.
你要去哪里?
Were are you going?
你们都反对是么?
You're all against this, right?
都要坚持原则抗命不遵?
And you're all gonna stand on principleand refuse to do it, right?
我要去Cuddy那里请旨
I'm going to get cuddy's approval.
Hannah母亲的事 还要瞒她多久?
how long are we gonna keep hannah in the dark about her mother?
越久越好
long as possible.
应该强制配备侧气囊的,(保护头部及胸腹的车内安全气囊)
Side airbag should be standard.
我肯定她会同意
I'm sure she'll agree.
她应该被告知母亲的处境
she should know her mother's situation.
通知消息是外科医生的事了
Breaking that newsis that surgeon's problem.
House那里有消息么?
Any word from house?
- 没有,- 也许Cuddy会反对
- No.,- Maybe cuddy will say no.
Cuddy从不反对(House)
Cuddy never says no.
不是这样的
That's not true.
没人说过不
Nobody ever says no.
我们不反对
We don't say no.
是你不反对
You don't say no.
他会回来 吹胡子瞪眼 给出七大理由
He'll come back,he'll browbeat us, he'll give us seven reasons,
最终我们放弃
and eventually we'll fold.
我们都会 不只是我
We all will,not just me.
避免脊髓神经切片的唯一途径是
The only way we can avoidbiopsying this kid's spine
另寻他法找到病因
is to find the answersome other way.
所有测试结果都是阴性
All the tests were negative.
需要更详尽的病史
We need a better history.
你还需要哪些文档?
How much more paper work do you need?
已经有了儿科记录  一打急诊记录
We've got pediatric records, a few dozen E.R.Records,
入院问卷
our own admission questionnaire.
你头一个问题是什么?
What's the first question?
保险条款
Insurance coverage.
好吧 第二个
Okay, second question.
直接说就好了
Just make your point.
哪里疼?
Where does it hurt?
如果知道她哪疼 我们就可以诊断
If we knew where it hurt, we could diagnose her.
你知道无痛症感觉不到疼痛吧?
You do know cipa meansshe can't feel pain.
不 无痛症是说她对疼痛不敏感
No, cipa means she's insensitive to pain.
她还是有分散的神经纤维可以传导痛觉
She still has scattered nerve fibers that could conduct pain,
但信号传导不到大脑
ut the signals don't make it to the brain.
给她更多痛觉信号会怎么样?
What if we give her more pain signals?
很多痛觉信号
A lot more pain signals.
也许其中一些能传导成功
Maybe some of them will make it through.
你要折磨她?
You wanna torture her?
不
No.
对别人是折磨
Yes.We do this to anybody else, it's torture.
对她 和扎扎手指头没区别
Doing it to her is no different than pricking her finger.
在她身上刺探
We keep poking sharp sticks into her,
直至找到本就疼痛的地方
eventually we'll find the part that's already tender.
院长干什么?
So what does a dean of medicine do?
能不能不谈工作?
Oh, can we please not talk about that?
别的都畅谈不忌
I will talk about anything else.
我只想逃离工作
I'm just trying to get away from work.
你作比喻吧
Metaphorically.
因为这家和医院毗邻的咖啡店
Because geographically, the coffee place around the corner
不是你能到达最远的距离吧
from the hospital probably isn't the furthest you could get.
但你看这雪
Well, the snow.
道路在清理
Roads are clearing.
但这儿撤退起来方便
But it's a good place to beat a retreat from.
你对约会不寄予很高期望?
You usually expect your dates to go wrong?
我学会要找条撤离的路径
Experience has taught me to have an escape route.
放低期望值 我的最爱之一
Well, low expectations,that's in my favor.
不管发生什么
Whatever happens...
你要明白 我生活中
I need you to understand that there are certain
有些恼人的部分
aspects to my life I'm no happy about.
要做脊髓神经切片
I need the nerve biopsy.
你亲自跑来对我说
And you hato come here personally to tell me that.
你怎么知道我在这儿?
And how did you even know I was here?
我得拿文件来
I had to bring the file.
这里是步行可达范围内最无需承诺的地方
This was the most non committal location in walking distance.
你的车钥匙放在桌上
You left your car keys on your desk.
Greg house!
Greg House!
你们肯定是网上认识的
You two must have met on line.
不然 肯定是恨你的朋友撮合的
Either that or you've got a friend who secretly hates you.
Uh, don herrick.
Don Herrick
我们通过单身爱舞网站认识
Yeah, we connected through single ballroom dance lovers.Com
他为什么不打自招?
why would he volunteer that information?
我为什么要隐瞒?
Why would I hide it?
你没警告他别多嘴,不然都会被我利用打击你
You didn't tell him that anything he said would be held against you.
你干什么的?
So what line of work are you in?
汽车维护
Oh, auto maintenance.
更换滤清器
Changing oil and filters.
太好了 我去的那家乱收费
Great, my place over charges.
不能相信你们这些人所说的
Can't trust anything you guys say.
你的店在哪里?
Where're you located?
分布在14个州
In 14 states.
我是东部润滑油的老板
I own eastern lube.
无痛症通常并发感染 她发烧
Most cipa complications are infection, and she's got a fever.
腰椎穿刺 尿检?
Lp?Urine?
正常 没有发现
Clean, normal.
白细胞计数也正常
Same with the white blood cell count.
癌症?
Cancer?
扫描没有发现
Nothing on the scan.
我认为是神经紊乱了温度控制
I think it's her nerves messing with the temperature control.
淀粉样变性病 肉瘤样病
Amyloid, sarcoid.
候选者太多
There's a lot of candidates.
需要做活检
I want a biopsy.
好吧
Fine.
非得这样 你就去做
If that's what you need,go get it.
他比那"小巫要个爸爸"网站的家伙好多了
He seems a lot nicer than that one from wicca need a daddy figure dot com.
一杯温水 一杯滚烫
One of these is warm, the other is very hot.
从这杯开始 再放入那杯
Start here,move to the hot one.
停留几秒钟 再重复
Just a few seconds.Then back.
我们监控你脑部活动
We're gonna monitor activity in your brain while you do it.
要是你感到热 可能是血管疾病
If you feel any response to the heat, it could indicate a vascular problem.
我妈妈怎么样了?
How's my mom doing?
她还好
she's okay.
你有感觉吗?
Do you feel anything?
没有 还好是什么意思?
No.What does okay mean?
她还在手术中
She's still in surgery.
据说会没事
They tell me it's going okay.
可以把手拿出来了
You can take your hand out.
你怎么不问更多?
And you didn't ask anything else?
把手从水杯里拿出来
Take your hand out of the water.
我妈妈到底怎么了?
What's going on with my mother?
Hannah.
Hannah
你让自己二级烧伤了
You just got second degree burns.
我没事
I'll be fine.
我妈妈怎么样了?
What's going on with my mother?
她会死吗?
Is she gonna die?
据说她会好起来
They said she's okay.
有内伤时 长时间的手术很平常
Surgery this long is typical when there are internal injuries.
注入纳络酮(解麻醉剂中毒)和蛋白激酶
Naloxone and kinase proteins in.
这样我就会感到疼了?
And that's gonna make me feel pain?
你们用螺栓固定我脑袋时 我没一点感觉
I didn't feel anything when you guys screwed this thing into my head.
这将替换你神经中的化学物质
It'll replace missing chemicals in your nerves.
提高灵敏度
Heightened sensitivity.
就要在你颅骨上钻孔
We'll be drilling directly into your skull.
如果你有感觉 可能是肉瘤
A response could indicate sarcoma.
是什么感觉?
What does it feel like?
很疼
It...hurts.
抱歉
Um...sorry.
骨痛是最厉害的
Bone pain is the worst there is.
你有了感觉马上告诉我们
So you need to let know as soon as you feel anything.
可以开始
She's ready.
你们在我头上钻洞时 我就干坐着?
So what...I just sit here while you guys drill a hole in me?
能说说话吗?
You wanna talk?
就你和妈妈两个?
Just you and your mom, huh?
你们肯定很亲近
You two must be pretty close.
是的
We were.
直到我被拘留
Until I got arrested.
第三次
The third time.
- 毒品,- 打架
Drugs?Fights.
你有优势
You got an advantage.
也不是
Not really.
不知道什么时候该停
Never know when to stop.
你跟很多人作对 还是你只想惹恼你妈妈?
You piss a lot of people off or are you just trying to piss off your mom?
其实只有这两个选择
Those are pretty much the only two choices you have.
Hannah 你要我们停下吗?
Hannah?You want us to stop?
停下颅钻
Stop the drill.Stop the drill.
没事了
It's okay.
什么感觉?
What'd you feel?
哪里有感觉?
Where did you feel it?
Hannah 我得知道你哪里疼
Hannah, I need to know how it hurt.
Hannah!
我厌倦了
I am so tired of this.
你知道心血管科新来的护士
Did you know that the new nurse from cardiologyis sleeping with
和董事局的怪律师好上了?
that weird lawyer from the board?
有11根手指的家伙?
The guy with 11 fingers?
他有11根手指?
He has 11 fingers?
你怎么会没注意到?
How do you not notice that?
那个护士曾经是男人
The nurse used to be a man.
她现在不是了?
She's not anymore?
我们不说这些
But we can't talk about that.
我们在说
I thought we were.
我们本来要谈这些的
We were supposed to talk about that.
我来就是告诉你这个
I came here to talk about that.
可来的路上 我遇到Cameron
But on the way up,I ran into cameron.
你有个无痛症患者
You've got a cipa patient.
变性护士更有趣
Mmm.Tranny nurse is more interesting.
这可有趣多了
Oh, it's way more interesting.
可我又得当你的良心
But instead, I've gotta be your damn conscience.
我厌倦唤起你的道德观念
I'm tired of being your conscience.
我不享受当你的良心
I don't enjoy being your conscience.
- 没人享受,- 你在研究她
- No one enjoys...,- you're studying her.
她确实病了
She's actually sick.
你把她绑走后才发现的
Which you found out after you took her on.
我好奇
I was curious.
因为我不是猫 好奇不危险,(谚语: 好奇害死猫)
Since I'm not a cat,that's not dangerous.
这句谚语不是用来警惕猫的
I don't think that metaphor was designed to actually warn cats.
你不关心她的病情 你在乎的是无痛症
You don't care about her illness, you care about cipa.
你的注意力集中在获取你的答案,而不她的
Which means your focus is gonna be on getting your answers, not hers.
谢谢
Thank you.
先有所知 先有所备
Forewarned is forearmed.
你想弄明白什么?
What do you think you're gonna figure out?
你以为她缺少痛觉的症状,能解决你的疼痛?
You think her lack of pain is somehow the answer to your pain.
要是你不跟Cameron说话 当下
I think if you'd stop talking to cameron, then right now,
我们就可以给护士排排名次
we could be ranking nurses in order of do-ability.
有情况
Need you.
脊椎神经切片有发现?
What did the nerve biopsy show?
没做
Never did it.
那就做
Then do it.
- 做不了,- 为什么?
- Can'T.,- Why?
她要从大厅扶栏往下跳
She's gonna jump off the lobby balcony.
你觉得我接得住她?
You think I can catch her?
离远点!
Get away from me!
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you.
你会
Yes, you are.
你嫉妒我什么都能做
You're just jealous that I can do anything.
Hannah出现了迫害妄想
Hannah, you're having a paranoid delusion.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
觉得她会跳
Think she would
这是真的 你们要我痛苦
this is real.You want me to be in pain.
你们自己说的
You even said so.
如果我们想伤害你 不会拦着你
If we wanted to hurt you, we'd let you jump.
让我看看我妈
Just let me see my mother.
好 这就带你去手术观察室
Fine, we'll take you to her O.R.Observation room.
不相信你!
I don't believe you!
你妈妈没事
Your mother is fine.
我刚和她外科医生谈过
I just spoke to her surgeon.
我不相信你!
I don't believe you!
Hannah 你要我们怎么做?
Hannah, what do you want from us?
要我们做什么?
What do you want us to do?
我感觉不到腿
I can't feel my legs.
你要是想在10分钟内故技重施
If you're trying to pull the same stunt twice in ten minutes...
不是装出来的
I'm not pretending.
腿不疼 感觉不到了
They don't hurt,they're just not there.
有感觉吗?
Anything?
不只是疼痛感
We're not looking for pain.
- 什么感觉都行 刺压?,- 没感觉
Anything at all,pressure?Nothing.
你六根骨头碎了
You have  six broken  bones,
发烧 脑震荡 心律不齐
a fever,a concussion,erratic heart rhythms,
腰部之下完全失去知觉
and a complete lack of sensation below the waist.
我感觉挺好
I feel fine.
我妈妈手术做完了吗?
Is my mother out of surgery yet?
还没有
Not yet.
幸运极了
This is excellent.
妄想症状消失了
The paranoia seems to have dissipated.
但生命垂危
But her vitals keep getting worse.
可能会在数小时内死去
She could be dead in hours.
如果饱受煎熬慢慢死去
But...if you're gonna die a miserable,lingering death,
没有痛觉幸运至极
pain-free is the way to do it.
你确定不是跌落导致瘫痪?
You sure the fall didn't cause the paralysis?
瘫痪导致跌落
The paralysis caused the fall.
脊椎没事
Spine's clean.
没有骨折或脊髓损伤
No veritable fractures or spinal cord compression.
更好了
Even better.
疯疯癫癫还瘫痪
The nuttiness and paralysis
意味着一定有某个神经部件出问题
mean there's definitely  a neurological component.
可能是神经病变
Could be a nerve disease.
所以我们需要检查神经切片,你却没有做
Which is why we need to look at the nerve that you didn't biopsy.
还有别的检查
There are other tests...
艾滋病 梅毒?
HIV? Syphilis?
所有性病检测都呈阴性,血管疾病 不 抗核抗体呈阴性
She's negative Vascular?>No.ANA was negative.
脑栓 不 核磁共振
Cerebral clot? No,MRI was...
甲亢危象,(甲亢病程中出现的一种严重并发症)
Thyroid storm.
有理 她糖反映迟缓
Makes sense,given her glucose reaction was slow
血钾也降低了
and potassium's down.
没错
Yeah.
我去和内分泌学家会诊
I'll check with an endocrinologist.
Bennett值班
Bennett's on call.
太好了
Perfect.
不是吧
No.
需要会诊
Need a consult.
我已经同意了你做神经切片
I already okayed your nerve biopsy.
需要内分泌学家
Need an endocrinologist.
Bennett值班
Bennett's on call.
不接电话
Won't pick up.
他的手机肯定坏了
His cell phone must be broken.
我的手机可没坏
Mine's working.
必须给你看资料
Had to give you the file.
我猜你怀疑是甲亢危象
I assume you're thinking thyroid storm.
有没有做激素检测?
Have you done a hormone panel?
正常 促甲状腺激素水平较低
Normal. TSH was on the low side.
壁炉是不是烧着火?
Is that a cheery fire I hear crackling nearby?
没有
No.
CPK(肌酸磷酸激酶)怎么样?
What about CPK enzymes?
提高了 275
Elevated. 275.
人家若是为了自己点燃炉火
People light fires for themselves.
定然不会矢口否认
But then they don't deny it.
他在这儿
He's here.
CPK还不够高
CPK isn't high enough.
血钾提高是因为支气管扩张剂的缘故
Potassium's what you'd expect because of the bronchodilators.
老天!
Oh,my God!
你没戴文胸
You're not wearing a bra.
这不是甲亢危象
It's not thyroid storm.
你们才刚见面
You just met him.
我喜欢他
I like him.
也喜欢做爱
And I like sex.
用不用我在胸口刺上字?
Do I need to stitch a letter on my tops?
不用
No.
不过或许可以在当地报纸上登个广告
But it might be worth taking out an ad in the local papers.
你喜欢我吗 House?
Do you like me,House?
我15分钟前刚和Bennett通过电话
I was on the phone with Bennett 15 minutes ago.
他的手机没出问题
His cell phone's working.
你原本不惜一切躲避我
You're M.O. is to avoid me at all costs.
突然 你需要我拨一拨 你动一动
And suddenly, you need my input on every move you make.
我只好认为 这是因为我在约会
I can only assume it's because I'm on a date.
见面时 我注意到
When we met, I noticed--
你注意到他是秘密兄弟会员,因他头发分路样子
You noticed he was a Shriner because the way he parted his hair.
你注意到他是个乖宝宝
You noticed he was a mama's boy
因为他眨左眼的样子
because of the way he blinked his left eye.
我不感兴趣 我不受你影响
I'm not interested. I'm not impressed.
只有两个原因
There are only two reasons
有人想要破坏我今晚的好事
anyone would want to screw with me tonight.
要么 他是个无私的正派人
Either they're an altruistic,
只是为了我的幸福着想
decent person who is worried about my well being...
要么他是自己想得到我
Or they want me FOR THEMSELVES
你漏了第三个可能性
You left out the third option.
想破坏别人幸福的魔鬼
Evil bastard who just wants to mess with other people's happiness.
晚安 House
Good night,House.
不会再有打扰了
We won't be bothered again.
太晚了
It's late.
- 我该走了,- 为什么?
- I should go.,- Why?
我把头发分在左边,还是个秘密兄弟会成员
I part my hair on hae left and I'm a Shriner.
你听到谈话了
You heard the conversation.
我对他不感兴趣
I'm not interested in him.
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
我这么说 只是让他不要再回来
I only said those things so that he wouldn't come back.
我并不热衷于我的工作
I don't really care about my job.
我干得不错 提供服务
I do it well, I provide a service.
但我的目标是赚足够的钱
But my goal was always to make enough money
去做我真正喜欢的事
to do the things I really like.
音乐 旅行
Music,travel...
这些我也喜欢
I like those things too.
你是喜欢 但这些对你并不至关重要
You like them,but they're not really important to you.
我不知道是因为House
I don't know whether it's House,
你的工作 还是冲突让你生机勃勃
your job,or if you just thrive on conflict,but...
你该留意 你跟他说话时候的样子
you should hear yourself when you're talking to him.
心无旁骛
Nothing else in the world is going on.
你专心 自信 夺目
You're focused, confident,compelling.
别误解了
Don't take this the wrong way,
我想跟那个女人约会
but I'd like to go out with that woman.
我可以让她听电话
I can get her on the phone.
你去了哪里?
Where did you go?
她情况更糟了
She's getting worse.
不是甲亢危象
It's not thyroid storm.
做脊髓神经切片
Get me spinal nerve.
还有别的检测
There are still r tests.
她刚说了女孩在恶化
She just said the girl was getting worse.
你们还想等待
You wanna wait.
会有感染的风险 还可能使瘫痪恶化
We'll be risking infection,maybe make the paralysis worse.
已经恶化了
It is worse.
我们让它越来越糟 做切片
We're making it worse than worse.Do the biopsy.
可能会使她瘫痪 却一无所获
We could paralyze her and get no useful information.
做切片
Do the biopsy.
如果是外周神经疾病
If you're thinking peripheral neuropathy,
该选择离脊髓稍远的神经
we should a take a nerve a little further away from the spine.
离真相也远了
A little further from the truth.
牵涉到瘫痪
We're talking paralysis.
很有可能是脊髓相关
Good chance the spine is relevant.
若病情发展
And if this thing is progressive,
要不了几小时 她就死了
it'll kill her in hours.
把论文还给我
Give me back my papers.
他是不是坚持要脊髓神经?
Is he asking for a spinal nerve?
你怎么知道?
How did you know?
让我们单独谈
Give us a venute.
你可知道 最近发现一种蛋白质,能加速神经生长?
Did you know they recently found a protein that speeds up nerve growth?
多奇妙
Fascinating stuff.
如果在脊髓神经的绝缘层放上这种蛋白质
If you put that protein with the insulation from a spinal nerve,
就能种植自己的小花园
you could grow your own little garden.
- 如果这根脊髓神经,- 是 是
- If that spinal nerve...,- Yeah,yeah,yeah.
如果恰好是来自无痛病患者
If it happened to come from a person with CIPA,
那就可以培育无痛觉神经,并植入自己的腿
I could grow pain-free nerves and graft them into my own leg.
好个邪恶的计划
What an evil plan.
你得终身用免疫抑制剂
You'd have to be on immunosuppressors for life.
冒感染的风险 缩短寿命
Risking infection, shorter life span...
短是短 可正常了
Shorter. But normal.
嫉妒通常表现的方式
Usually jealousy expresses itself
是想摧毁别人拥有的
by trying to destroy what someone has.
你更雄心勃勃
You're more ambitious.
你想歪曲医学事实来达到目的
You actually wanna change medical fact to get this thing...
医学事实一直在变化
Medical fact changes all the time.
你用患者的生命来冒险
You're risking your patient's life.
这样医学事实才会进步
That's how medical fact changes.
医生冒险
A doctor risks--
是为了患者的健康
To serve their patient's health.
不是为了自己的
Not their own.
这诊断没有错
This is medically justified.
你确定?
Are you sure?
你肯定
Are you sure...
你能够做这个判断?
that you're the right one to be making this call?
切片检查能安全取得的神经
Biopsy whatever nerve you figure you can safely get at.
天 Wilson真是讨厌
GOd,Wilson's annoying.
情人节凌晨3点
Past 3:00 AM on Valentine's Day night.
我知道你和Wendy有约
I assume you had a date with Wendy.
她没事 知道规矩
She'll survive. She knows the deal.
你真幸运
You're lucky.
我是
I know.
以后等有了时间
Someday,when thers time,
我也想有社交生活
I would like to actually have a social life.
有朝一日?
Someday?
一个漂亮的女人
Come on.If there's one thing a good-looking woman
想要社交生活最容易不过
can have when she wants, it's a social life.
你指性爱生活
You mean a sex life.
有个陪伴不是错
There's nothing wrong with a little companionship
在认真的感情到来之前
'til the real thing comes along.
我有过认真的感情
I had the real thing.
我只是不想安定下来
Forgive me if I don't want to settle.
是么
Right.
这什么意思?
What does that mean?
没什么
Nothing.
你认为我没有过真正的感情?
You think I didn't have the real thing?
我不知道你有过什么
I have no idea what you had.
而你就下了判断
And yet you're judging it.
熬夜让我暴躁 对不起
It's late,I'm cranky.Sorry.
你认为我没有过真情?
You think I didn't have the real thing.
你根本不知道
How could you even know?
你和一个垂死的男人结婚
You married a dying man.
你想的是 6个月或一年 会很艰难
You thought...six months,a year, it'll be tough.
但我能挺过来 还能继续自己的生活
But then I'll recover and I'll have the rest of my life.
就好像不小心得感冒
It's like willy-nilly  getting the flu
或是不得已加入和平队,(文化外交志愿者)
or joining the Peace Corps.
短期的
Short term.
一针见血
Wow,you nailed it.
就好比是浪费的周末
It's basically like a wasted weekend.
你做出的牺牲是巨大的
The sacrifices you made were huge.
但你对他的爱仅此而已
But they were at the height  of your love for him.
承诺之所以是承诺
A commitment is only commitment
是因为没有到期日
because it has no expiration date.
你站在一人身旁
You stand next to someone
看他用牙线30年
and watch them floss for 30 years,
像我父母那样
like my parents have,
这才叫牺牲
then ask for sacrifices.
才会懂得什么叫做真感情
That's how you know the real thing.
Cameron...
Cameron
我不是指责你
I wasn't criticizing you.
躲避承诺的人 明白它有多沉重
People who avoid commitment are people who know what a big thing it is.
这不对劲
This isn't right.
无痛症不会导致这样的变性
CIPA can't cause this much degeneration.
从中央切取的一些神经纤维
A few nerve fibers we teased out of the center
还有部分绝缘层
have some insulation left.
但神经束周围的绝缘层都剥落了
But the insulation around the bundles has been stripped bare.
意味着损伤是来自外部
Means the damage must be coming from the outside in.
这是次发脱髓鞘病变
Which means it's secondary demyelination.
病源在别处
Which means the source is somewhere else.
不是神经疾病
Which tells us it's not a nerve disease,
是全身性的病 影响到了神经
it's something systemic that's affecting the nerves.
我们该
Which means that we need to--
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
孩子的妈妈终于手术告一段落
Kid's mom is finally out of surgery.
去去就来
I'll be right back.
那又怎样?
So what?
Hannah该见见她
Hannah should see her.
在我们讨论完怎么救她后,她马上就能去
Yes,immediately after we're done chatting about saving her life.
最有可能是代谢类疾病
Most likely causes are metabolic.
她脑肿胀
They found brain swelling.
就要准备让她做另一项手术
They're prepping her mother for another surgery.
那又怎样?
Again,so what?
叫个护士送孩子去
Get a nurse to take the kid.
有多过60种代谢类疾病
There are more than 60 different metabolic conditions
会引起她现在的症状
that could account for what she's got.
我可只有你们3个人
There's only three of you guys.
她吓坏了
She's scared.
肯定的
She should be.
如果我们不诊断出 她会死
She'll die if we don't diagnose her.
那就诊断出她
So diagnose her.
妈
Mom.
有多严重?
How bad is it?
你好吗?
Are u OK?
我没事 妈妈
I'm okay,Mom.
我会好的 我总是会好
I'll get better. I always get better.
你检查过自己了 量体温?
Are you checking yourself? Your temperature?
妈妈 你能不能别管了?
Mom,could you just let it go?
你现在不该担心
You shouldn't be worrying.
宝贝 是我不好
Oh,baby,I'm sorry.
我该留心有车子开过来
I should have  seen that car coming.
不
No.
我是自作自受
I did this to myself. I screwed up.
你是对的 我错了
You were right You were right and I was wrong.
不
No.No.
我不该下雪天跑出去
I...I shouldn't have gone out on the ice.
我不该摔跤
I shouldn't have  fallen down.
我不该让你
And I shouldn't have made you rush me
今年第十次送我进急诊室
to an ER for the tenth time this year.
妈?
Mom?
妈妈 你怎么了?
Mom? You okay?
得送她继续去做手术
We gonna have to take her  back to surgery.
Hannah 你的血压升高
Hannah,your BP is way up.
得休息一下
We need to get you some rest.
我的手湿了
My hand's wet.
你哭了
You're crying.
我不会哭
I can't cry.
头疼死了
My head is killing me.
疼痛能告诉我们什么?
So what does the pain tell us?
没有刺痛麻痒 可以排除
No tingling, no itching, so we can rule out--
什么都证实不了
It tells us nothing.
不是身体疼痛 是情感
It wasn't physical pain, it was emotional.
没错
Exactly.
她有了头痛时 她们在干什么?
What were they doing when she got the headache?
说再见
Saying good-bye.
你说她们在争执
You said they were arguing.
她们不是真的吵架
They weren't really arguing.
她只是很沮丧
She was just frustrated.
她们在吵什么?
What were they arguing about?
谁的过错
Whose fault it was.
外周神经疾病 发烧
Peripheral neuropathy, fever,
间歇性妄想症
and intermittent paranoia.
很多代谢疾病都能引发
Lots of metabolic conditions can explain those things.
再加上内疚会怎样?
But what if we add guilt?
内疚作为症状?
Guilt as a symptom?
阿尔兹海默症能引发欣快,疼痛引发消沉
Alzheimer's can cause euphoria,pain causes depression,
维生素B12缺乏引发内疚
and B12 deficiency causes guilt.
综合其他的
Along with all that other stuff.
如果她感到内疚
If she felt guilty,
就不会让她妈妈生活不好过
she wouldn't be making her mother's life miserable.
她就不会打架
She wouldn't be  getting in fights,
被拘留
getting arrested...
也许她打架就是因为感到内疚
Maybe she's fighting  because she feels guilty.
她想证明给妈妈看,即使胡乱犯险 她还能平安
She's showing her mom she can take stupid risks and still be safe.
那妈妈就不必担心
Means mom can let go.
这是有逻辑的思维
Which is rational.
如果内疚是疾病引起的症状
If guilt is a symptom,it's caused by the illness,
而不是思维过程的产物
not by a thought process.
而且应该是新的症状
And it would  have to be new.
几年前 她是模仿学生
Couple years ago, she was a model student.
没意义 如果头痛是由内疚引起的
This is pointless.If the headache  was caused by guilt,
她缺乏维生素B12
she has a B-12 deficiency.
如果只是因为她心里难过
If it's just because she was sad,
那就没办法 用什么来证明?
it's meaningless. How the hell  do we test for that?
不必 给她一剂维生素B12
We don't.We give her a shot of B12.
如果她转好 那我是对的
When she gets better, I was right.
已经给了
We already did.
急诊室在她入院时就给过B12
ER gave her B12 when she was admitted.
多种维生素补充剂
Part of a multi-vitamin supplement.
很明显 她是难过
Apparently, she's just sad.
你怎么还没走?
Why are you still here?
想让病人试验一下新药
Trying to get a couple patients into a drug trial.
明天要交书面文件
Paperwork's due tomorrow.
你为什么还在?
Why are you here?
还没找出为什么
Still haven't figured out why...
不 你为什么来这儿 我的办公室
No,I meant here.In my office.
刚推翻了一个很妙的B12缺乏症理论
Just dumped a cool B12 theory.
在考虑白血病
Moved on to leukemia.
这个老套点
Very pedestrian.
我乐不起来
I'm not happy.
她白细胞计数很低
Her white blood cell count was low.
可她又有
But the one she's got...
很多嗜曙红细胞(白细胞的一种)
A whole lot of eosinophils.
免疫球蛋白E的水平到了临界点
The immunoglobin E level's borderline.
想要有100%的把握
If you wanna be 100% sure,
检查骨髓
check the bone marrow.
已经在做活检了
Team's doing a biopsy right now.
原来
So it turns out...
那个怪律师
the weird lawyer...
知道她曾是个男人
knew that she used to be a man.
他无所谓?
And he's cool with that?
原来他的前女友也曾是男人
Turns out that his previous girlfriend also used to be a man.
- 噢!,- 是啊
- Ho-ho!,- Yeah.
你能不能安分地看着我吃?
Is it possible  for you to just watch me eat?
还是你有原始冲动
Or do you get some primeval thrill
要击败别的狩猎者 争夺食物?
out of beating  the other hunters to the food?
回头见
See ya later.
你还不明白我不需要镇静剂?
You still haven't figured out that I don't need sedation?
这样才能保证你不会乱动
It's so you don't move during the procedure.
这是氧化亚氮吗?
Is that nitrous?
你想要杀了她?,(NO会抑制维生素B12的合成)
You trying to kill her?
在做脑电图的时候就曾给她用过氧化亚氮
You gave her nitrous during the EEG.
这才让恶势力抬起了头
That's what made this thing rear its ugly head.
什么东西?
What thing?
B12缺乏症
B12 deficiency.
你有没有觉得这似曾相识?,我们讨论过了
Are you having deja vu? We've had this conversation.
她用过B12 没有好转
She was given B12. She didn't get better.
因为被别的东西吃了
Because someone else ate it.
做腹部的核磁共振成像
Get an abdominal MRI.
什么?
What?
你们要干什么?
What are you doing?
别碰我!
Don't touch me!
瞧 她来了
See,there she goes.
又有迫害妄想
Another paranoid delusion.
不行 照这个速度恶化
Come on. At the rate she's going downhill,
来不及做核磁共振 得做手术
forget the MRI, we need an O.R.
别碰我!
Leave me alone!
在使用中!
Occupied!
她的疝气等不了,(疝: 脐部隆起肿块)
Her hernia can wait.
救命 他们想害我!
Help! They're trying to kill me!
你可以相信她 我们想害她
Okay,you can either believe that we really are trying to kill her...
要么你可以认为她受到病症的驱使
Or you can assume that she's suffering from a medical condition.
鉴于这里是医院 我们穿得像医生
Seeing as this is a hospital and we're all  dressed like doctors,
有更简便的方法杀人
and there are easier ways to kill somebody...
Bev 帮他们
Bev,help them.
需要碘酒 10号和15号解剖刀
Gonna need iodine, scalpels number 10 and 15,
镊子 和一个大色拉碗
forceps, and a largish salad bowl.
把她按住
Okay,hold her down.
快点 女士 她进入角色了
Come on,weenies, she's in a cast.
药签
Swab.
15号
15.
你不麻醉她?
You're not gonna anesthetize her?
没事 变个戏法
Relax,it's just a magic trick.
她是装出来的
She's faking it.
这次可不会上当
We're not falling for it this time.
收回那套吧
Okay,keep that retracted.
镊子
Forceps.
去湖边钓鱼很好玩
Lake fishing can be fun.
能拉近家人的关系
It can bring the generations together.
可要是鲑鱼和鲈鱼没有煮熟
But if you don't cook that trout or perch well,
你就给这家伙提供住宿和膳食了,(绦虫: 肠道寄生虫 带状 可长达10米)
you'll be giving room and board to this fella.
所谓免费膳食就是摄入的所有维生素B12
And by free board,I mean all the B12 you can take in.
我体内也会有绦虫吗?
I could have tapeworm in me?
不可能
Not likely.
那样你会疼死
You'd be in a lot of pain.
得有25英尺长 (7.5米)
It's gotta be 25 feet long.
该死
Dammit.
世界纪录超过60英尺(20米)
World record's over 60.
Hannah 醒醒
Hannah. Wake up.
有人来看你
Somebody here to see you.
她左半边不能动
She's got limited motion  on her left side.
你得照看她一段时间
You might have to take care of her for a while.
噢 噢
Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
虽然你感觉不到
You don't feel it,
别把缝线撕裂了
but you're about to rip your stitches out.
好好照顾自己
Take care of yourself.
才能照顾好她
Then you can take care of her.
你还没回家
You haven't gone home.
对不起 没能过情人节
Sorry I screwed up Valentine's Day.
我是跟医生约会
I'm dating a doctor.
我不是白痴 有心理准备
I'd be an idiot to expect anything else.
有个礼物给你
I did get you a gift.
MGH (马萨诸塞州总医院)
MGH.
波士顿最好的教学医院
Best teaching hospital in Boston.
想从事护士行业
You wanna be a nurse practitioner,
那里是最好的
that's as good as it gets.
我打了几个电话
I made a few calls.
你想去就能去
You're in if you want it
这就是你帮我争取
This is why you've been helping me get
手术室小时数 来获得资格?
my surgical hours for accreditation?
- 我以为你想要,- 好傻
I thought you wanted-- Stupid.
你划下10英尺的私人空间距离
You've got ten feet of personal space around you.
我走近一步 你后退一步
I step forward,  you step back.
我很多事都跟你说
I've shared a lot of things with you.
所以你才要跟我分手
Which is why you're breaking up with me.
你受不了亲密
You can't stand to be close.
Wendy.
Wendy
难道你对我发怒 我就会继续和你在一起?
You think I'll stay with you because you're angry with me?
我是难过
I'm upset.
因为我在乎
Because I care.
只有你们才觉得吵架也得有逻辑
Only you'd expect an argument to be rational.
你和你的混蛋上司
You and that ass boss of yours.
你可以向她要脊神经
You could ask her for the spinal nerve.
她凭什么给我?
She's got no reason to give it.
她欠你的
She owes you.
医院会给她寄账单
The hospital will send her a bill.
依我
I'm just saying.
你该趁她维生素B12尚缺乏时动手
If you wanna do it,do it while her B12 is still low.
有内疚伴随你不错
Guilt can be your friend.
吃早饭?
Breakfast?
好
Yeah.
情人节快乐!
Happy Valentine's Day.
给那些已经成双对的人过的节日
A holiday that only applies to people who are already paired up.
对于别的人 只是星期三
For everyone else, it's Wednesday.
谢谢你泼我冷水
Thank you for that dash of cold water.
别误会
Don't get me wrong,
我还是相信有真爱存在
I still think true love's out there,
只是非常遥远
it's just very far away.
有可能在另一个星系
Possibly in another galaxy.
得发明比光速更快的飞行方法
We may need to develop faster than light travel
我们才能联系上
before we can make contact.
我们做爱吧
So I'm thinking we should have sex.
这有道理
That makes sense.
除了流行歌曲的教条
Despite the wisdom of pop songs,
实在没必要在真爱到来前 浪费生命
there's no point in putting our lives on hold 'til love comes along.
我们都是健康忙碌的人
We're both healthy and busy people.
一起工作 这很方便
We work together, so it's convenient.
好比微波炉批萨?
Like microwave pizza?
在所有我共事的人中
And of all the people I work with,
你是我最不可能爱上的
you're the one I'm least likely to fall in love with.
好比微波炉批萨
Like microwave pizza.
是想让事情变得简单
The point here is to make things simpler,
不是更复杂
not more complicated.
也许以后会对谁动真情
Someday,there'll be time to get serious about someone.
当前 既然我们已经做过一次,感觉还不错
Meanwhile,we already had sex once and didn't get weird about it.
我明白
I get it. I get it.
如果我对你的评价感到恼火呢?
So what if I'm offended by your judgment?
那你就不是我要找的人
Then you're not the man I'm looking for.